Secret Mission is a drama, war film directed by Harold French.
World War II drama in which a member of the French Resistance and three British agents undertake a hazardous mission to
infiltrate a German HQ in search of vital information that could lead to the overthrow of the Nazis.
Major Peter Garnett, played by Hugh Williams.
Michele de Carnot, played by Carla Lehmann.
Captain Red Gowan, played by Roland Culver.
Private Nobby Clark, played by Michael Wilding.
Raoul de Carnot, played by James Mason.
Violette, housekeeper, played by Nancy Price.
Secret Mission is a 1942 British war film directed by Harold French and starring Hugh
Williams, James Mason, Nancy Price, Carla Lehmann and Roland Culver.
The tone is emotional.